University Photography Photograph Collection UA206
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 2005 -- 2006; UA206.001; 3347 Digital Object(s)
  - Job 050522 NSO Pre-Commencement, 2005; UA206.001.057; Sobecki, Nicki
    - A gathering at the Institute for Global Leadership and the Top of the Hill Tribute/Illumination Ceremony at Goddard Chapel during the 2005 Commencement weekend. Photo 0032, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.057.00006; Sobecki, Nicki
    - A gathering at the Institute for Global Leadership and the Top of the Hill Tribute/Illumination Ceremony at Goddard Chapel during the 2005 Commencement weekend. Photo 0016, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.057.00007; Sobecki, Nicki
    - A gathering at the Institute for Global Leadership and the Top of the Hill Tribute/Illumination Ceremony at Goddard Chapel during the 2005 Commencement weekend. Photo 0036, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.057.00008; Sobecki, Nicki
    - A gathering at the Institute for Global Leadership and the Top of the Hill Tribute/Illumination Ceremony at Goddard Chapel during the 2005 Commencement weekend. Photo 0030, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.057.00009; Sobecki, Nicki
    - A gathering at the Institute for Global Leadership and the Top of the Hill Tribute/Illumination Ceremony at Goddard Chapel during the 2005 Commencement weekend. Photo 0035, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.057.00010; Sobecki, Nicki
    - A gathering at the Institute for Global Leadership and the Top of the Hill Tribute/Illumination Ceremony at Goddard Chapel during the 2005 Commencement weekend. Photo 0015, 2005-05-21; UA206.001.057.00011; Sobecki, Nicki
  - Job 050522 WMA Commencement, 2005; UA206.001.058; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0132, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00001; Martin, Winslow
      Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel.
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0120, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00002; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0107, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00003; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0389, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00004; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0335, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00005; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0279, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00006; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0262, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00007; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0249, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00008; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0209, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00009; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0108, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00010; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0391, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00011; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0341, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00012; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0287, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00013; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0272, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00014; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0234, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00015; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0230, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00016; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0205, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00017; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0151, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00018; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0101, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00019; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0292, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00020; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0282, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00021; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0267, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00022; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0227, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00023; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0191, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00024; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0091, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00025; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0055, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00026; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0012, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00027; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0370, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00028; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0350, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00029; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0296, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00030; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0231, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00031; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0222, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00032; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0187, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00033; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0178, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00034; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0092, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00035; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0311, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00036; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0257, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00037; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0246, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00038; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0236, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00039; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0210, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00040; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0196, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00041; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0181, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00042; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0129, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00043; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0356, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00044; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0349, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00045; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0340, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00046; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0285, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00047; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0274, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00048; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0263, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00049; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0193, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00050; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0150, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00051; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0139, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00052; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0100, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00053; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0363, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00054; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0348, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00055; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0390, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00056; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0374, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00057; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0203, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00058; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0158, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00059; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0128, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00060; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0109, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00061; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0104, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00062; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0097, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00063; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0284, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00064; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0264, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00065; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0252, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00066; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0226, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00067; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0214, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00068; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0194, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00069; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0159, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00070; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0145, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00071; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0131, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00072; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0116, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00073; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0054, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00074; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0014, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00075; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0260, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00076; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0250, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00077; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0241, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00078; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0232, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00079; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0228, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00080; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0224, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00081; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0215, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00082; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0153, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00083; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0143, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00084; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0068, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00085; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0035, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00086; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0380, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00087; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0353, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00088; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0298, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00089; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0243, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00090; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0133, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00091; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0118, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00092; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0082, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00093; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0037, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00094; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0327, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00095; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0239, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00096; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0212, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00097; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0201, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00098; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0126, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00099; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0066, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00100; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0305, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00101; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0258, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00102; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0218, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00103; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0185, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00104; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0156, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00105; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0140, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00106; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0099, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00107; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0381, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00108; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0207, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00109; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0169, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00110; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0365, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00111; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0351, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00112; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0344, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00113; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0333, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00114; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0302, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00115; Martin, Winslow
    - Phase 1 of the 2005 Commencement ceremony and the drama department's Phase 2 ceremony in Goddard Chapel. Photo 0216, 2005-05-22; UA206.001.058.00116; Martin, Winslow
  - Job 050531 MKO Bharucha, 2005; UA206.001.059; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050601 MKO Coffin, 2005; UA206.001.060; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050603 MKO Dentists, 2005; UA206.001.061; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050609 MKO Manno, 2005; UA206.001.062; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050611 Edmundson, 2005; UA206.001.063; Unknown
  - Job 050615 MKO Nutrition, 2005; UA206.001.064; Ko, Melody
  - Job 050620 ASC Campus, 2005; UA206.001.065; Schutzengel, Aaron
  - Job 050620 BLO Campus, 2005; UA206.001.066; Loeb, Brian
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including the ASEAN Auditorium, the Jumbo statue, inside Tisch Library, construction on the roof of the Campus Center, and Goddard Chapel. Photo 073, 2005-06-20; UA206.001.066.00001; Loeb, Brian
      Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including the ASEAN Auditorium, the Jumbo statue, inside Tisch Library, construction on the roof of the Campus Center, and Goddard Chapel.
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including the ASEAN Auditorium, the Jumbo statue, inside Tisch Library, construction on the roof of the Campus Center, and Goddard Chapel. Photo 062, 2005-06-20; UA206.001.066.00002; Loeb, Brian
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including the ASEAN Auditorium, the Jumbo statue, inside Tisch Library, construction on the roof of the Campus Center, and Goddard Chapel. Photo 035, 2005-06-20; UA206.001.066.00003; Loeb, Brian
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including the ASEAN Auditorium, the Jumbo statue, inside Tisch Library, construction on the roof of the Campus Center, and Goddard Chapel. Photo 027, 2005-06-20; UA206.001.066.00004; Loeb, Brian
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including the ASEAN Auditorium, the Jumbo statue, inside Tisch Library, construction on the roof of the Campus Center, and Goddard Chapel. Photo 011, 2005-06-20; UA206.001.066.00005; Loeb, Brian
    - Stock photos of the Medford/Somerville campus, including the ASEAN Auditorium, the Jumbo statue, inside Tisch Library, construction on the roof of the Campus Center, and Goddard Chapel. Photo 002, 2005-06-20; UA206.001.066.00006; Loeb, Brian